Guide to the Charles Seymour Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1912-(1918-1922)-1963; Series I; 7'4" (20 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Class of 1925, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Cleveland, Reginald M., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Clifford, Philip G., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Clow, William E., Jr., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Cobb, Margaret A. (Mrs. Frank I.), 1928 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Coe, William R., 1951, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Coffin, Henry S., 1923, 1928, 1931, 1935, 1938, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 171)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 9/4
    - Colby, Bainbridge, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Collier, P. F., and Son Corporation, 1960, undated (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Collins, Philip H., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Colorado College, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Columbia University, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Comite d'Accueil de la Manifestation Herbert Hoover, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Commission d'Enquête, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Commission for Relief in Belgium Educational Foundation (Box 4, Folder 179)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 11/7
      See also: box 6, folder 323 box 11, folder 662
    - Committee on Public Information, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Conant, James B., 1949, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils
      See: box 84, folder 34a box 14, folder 848-869
    - Congdon, R. V., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Connecticut, University of, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Connor, Seymour
    - Cooksey, Mrs. C. D., n.y. (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Cooksey, Charlton, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Coolidge, Archibald, 1920, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Coombe, Reginald G., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Cooper, James Wayne, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Cooper, Starr G., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Cornell University, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Coromilas, L. A., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 190a)
    - Corwin, Edward S.
      See: box 7, folder 405
    - Corwin, Margaret, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 190b)
    - Corwin, Richard, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Cotner, Robert C., 1955 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 193)
      See also: box 4, folder 214
    - Coward, Thomas R., 1938, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Cowles, Edith (Madre Francesca Chiara), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Cox, Oscar, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 196)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 3/1
    - Crane, Joseph G., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Cravath, Paul, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Crawford, Albert B., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Crawford, David
      See: box 3, folder 173
    - Creel, George, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 200)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 1/2
    - Cross, Wilbur, 1917, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 201)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 1/4
      See also:
      See also: box 16, folder 942
    - Crowe, E. R., 1922 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Culbertson, William S., 1950, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Cullman, Howard S., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Current History, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Curtis, Edward E., 1922, undated (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Curtis, John G., 1920 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Curtis, Lewis P., 1954, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 208)
      See also: box 9, folder 552-553
    - Czechoslovak Commission
      See: box 8, folder 451
    - Dahl, Edward C.
      See: box 3, folder 159-163
    - Dahl, George
      See: See:/i>: box 3, folder 159-163
    - Danes, Gibson A., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Darcy, Edward S., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Darden, C. W.
      See: box 14, folder 848-869
    - Davidson, Eugene, 1935, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 211)
      See also: box 9, folder 552-553 box 86, folder 108a
    - Davidson, John W., 1956-1959, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 212)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 16/6
    - Davidson, Sidney W., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Davis, Norman, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Davis, Walter G., 1923, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, 1920, 1923, 1958, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Davison, H. P., Jr., 1919, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Day, Clive, 1908-1909, 1918, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 218)
      See also: box 46, folder 167-170
    - Day, Clive, 1924-1925, 1927-1928, 1930, 1936, undated (Box 4, Folder 219)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 4/8
    - Day, Edmund E., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Day, George Parmly, 1917, 1923, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Day, Huntington T.
      See: box 13, folder 812
    - Day, Katharine Seymour, 1954
    - Dealey, George B., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - de Baun, Lewis H., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - de Biasi, Agostino, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - De Golyer, Sydney B., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Delano, William A., 1949, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Dempsey, John B., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Denny, Austin F., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 228a)
    - Denton, Frances B., 1938, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 229)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 3/4
      See also: box 2, folder 102 box 11, folder 690-691
    - Department of Health (Yale), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - DeVane, William C., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - De Weerd, H. A., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - de Wiart, Hubert Carton, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - de Wolf, Francis C.
      See: box 1, folder 27
    - Deyo, John M., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Dickey, Charles D., 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Dickey, John, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Dictionary of American Biography, 1955, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Dillon, Read, and Company, Inc.
      See: box 11, folder 684-686
    - Dines, Tyson, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Documentary History of the Peace Conference, 1931 June - 1932 January (Box 4, Folder 239)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 8/4
    - Documentary History of the Peace Conference, 1932 February (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Dodd, Mead, and Company, 1934, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Dodd, William E., 1928-1929, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Dodds, Harold, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 243)
      See also: box 14, folder 848-869
    - Dodge, Bayard, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Dodge, John V.
      See: box 5, folder 267
    - Doggett, Ruth A., 1927 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Dollard, John, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Doob, Leonard W., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 247)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 7/5
    - Doolittle, Laura Seymour, 1951
    - Dos Passos, John, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Drake, Carl B., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Dreier, Katherine, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Drummond, Eric, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Dudley, L. P.
    - Duemling, Robert W., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Dulles, Allen, 1919-1920, 1922, 1934, 1936-1938, 1940, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 254)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 16/14
    - Dunbar, Noel, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Duncan, J. Donald, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Dunham, William H., Jr., 1949-1950, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Eaton, Mrs. Clara Gage, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 257a)
    - Ecklund, John E., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Ehrmann, Howard M., 1922, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P.
      See: box 1, folder 29
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 259a)
      See also: box 88
    - Eisenstadt, A. S., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Ela, Alfred, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Eliot, John G., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Eliot, Samuel A., 1926 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Elliot, Nellie P., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Ellis, Garrison McC., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Embree, William D., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1922-1923, 1925-1926, 1928-1929, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 267)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 18/8
      See also: box 7, folder 378 box 15, folder 899
    - English, Katharine Dana (Mrs. Philip H.), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Entes, David H., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Epler, Percy H., 1953-1954, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 270)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 16/3
    - Epler, Percy H., 1960 March-April (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Epler, Percy H., 1960 September - 1963 (Box 5, Folder 272)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 10/2
    - Sister Ethel Mary, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Evans, Paul D., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Fafella, Henry A., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Faile, E. H., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Fairchild, A. H. R., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Faix, Philip A., Jr., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Fales, Haliburton, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Farmer, Frances, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Farnam, Thomas W., 1923-1924, 1926-1928, 1933-1936, 1938, 1940-1941, undated (Box 5, Folder 281)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 15/13
    - Farrand, Max, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 281a)
    - Farrar, John, 1926, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Fay, Sidney B., 1921, 1929, 1932, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 283)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 4/10
    - Ferguson, David, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Ferrell, Robert H., 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 285)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 9/0
    - Ferrell, Robert H., 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Ferrin, Dana H., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Fesler, James W., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Fifer, Louis J., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Finley, David E., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Fischer, Louis, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - Fisher, H. H., 1928 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Fisher, Irving, 1917, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - Fisher, Samuel H., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Fiske, Robert B., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Fitzgerald, John H. (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Focillon, Henri
      See: box 11, folder 678
    - Focillon, Marguerite H. (Madame Henri Focillon), 1955-1956, 1958, undated (Box 5, Folder 297)
      See also: box 10, folder 646
    - Fodor, D. Nandor, undated (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Foord, Archie, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - Forbach, Arthur, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Ford, Guy Stanton, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 300a)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1935, 1953, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - Foreign Policy Association
      See: box 15, folder 889
    - Forman, Charles W., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - Forrest, Wilbur
    - Forster, Henry A., 1922, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - The Forum, 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - Foster, J. T., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 305)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 7/1
    - Fowler, George, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Fowler, Thomas, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Fraenkel, Peter, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Frank, Sidney J., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Fraser, Hugh R., 1940, undated (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Frazier, Arthur H., 1925, 1927, 1929, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Freed, Allie S., 1937 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Freedom Fund, Inc., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Freeman, John, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - French, Robert D., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 314a)
    - French, Miss
      See: box 14, folder 852
    - Freund, Gerald
    - Friend, Theodore, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Frissell, Sydney D., 1950, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Frueh, Nancy T. (Mrs. Alfred J., Jr.), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Fullerton, Morton, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Furniss, Edgar S., 1932,1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Gabriel, Ralph, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 320)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 1/9
    - Gabriel, Robert T.
      See: box 16, folder 934
    - Gage, Charles S., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Galloway, Eilene-Marie, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Galpin, Perrin C., 1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 323)
      See also: box 4, folder 179 box 7, folder 408-409
    - Gammell, William, Jr., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Garner, J. W., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Garrison, Elisha E., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Garver, Chauncey
    - Gasser, Albert, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Geddes, Sir Eric, 1923, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 328)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 5/3
    - Gelfand, Lawrence E., 1953, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Gerard, James W., 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 330)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 7/6
    - Gersony, J., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Gilbert, Charles H., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Glass, Carter, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Godley, Frederick A., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Gokey Company, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Gompers, Samuel
    - Gooch, George P., 1929, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 336)
      See also: box 12, folder 717-718
    - Goodhart, Arthur, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Gordon, David C.
      See: box 1, folder 26
    - Gore, Thomas P., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Gorrell, E. S., 1933 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Gotlieb, Howard, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 340)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 10/11
    - Gotlieb, Howard, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 341)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 19/10
    - Gotlieb, Howard, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 342)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 26/11
    - Gotlieb, Howard, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Gotlieb, Howard, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 344)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 14/1
    - Graves, Henry S., 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 345)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 17/15
    - Graves, Henry S., 1927 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Gray, John L., Jr.
    - Green, Theodore F.
      See: box 7, folder 408-409
    - Greene, Edward B., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Greene, Edward M., Jr., 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Greenleaf, John C., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Greenslet, Ferris
      See: box 7, folder 410-417
    - Greenwich Time, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Gregory, Thomas W., 1924, 1926, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 351)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 3/5
      See also: box 52, folder 259
      See also: The Vance McCormick Papers, MS 466
    - Grey, Viscount, of Fallodon, 1925-1926, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 352)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 4/6
      See also: box 52, folder 263
      See also: The Edward M. House Papers, MS 466
    - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1933-1936, 1957, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Grose, Peter B., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - Guggenheim Foundation
      See: box 2, folder 77 box 14, folder 848-869
    - Gulliver, Dean, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - Gummere, John, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - Hadden, Britten, 1923, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - Hadley Family, 1923, 1930, 1936-1941 (Box 6, Folder 358)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 15/3
    - Hadley, Morris, 1949-1950, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - Hall, Edward T., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - Hall, William E., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - Hamburger, Joseph, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 362)
    - Hamilton, John J., 1926 (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - Hannaford, John L., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - Hannaford, Jule M., Jr., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 365)
    - Hard, William, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Haring, C. H., 1917, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Harkness, Edward S., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Harkness, Mary (Mrs. Edward S.), 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 370)
      See also: box 8, folder 488
    - Harris, Lionel H., 1923 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - Harrison, Harry P., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - Hart, B. H. Liddell, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Hart, James P.
    - Haskell, C. D., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - Haskins, Charles S.
    - Hawes, Richard W., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Hawkins, R. C., 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - Hawley, Hudson R., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Hayes, Ralph, 1922-1923 (Box 7, Folder 378)
      box 5, folder 267
    - Haymaker, J. N., 1926 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Healey, Julia Davis (Mrs. Charles), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Heath, D. C., and Company
      See: See box 84, folder 25
    - Heckscher, August, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - Heffelfinger, F. Peavey, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - Heffernan, John B., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - Heineman, D. N., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - Heine-Geldern, Robert, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 384a)
    - Helms, Birch (also correspondence to Helms family re World War I and Peace Conference), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 385)
    - Hemingway, James S.
      See: box 10, folder 566
    - Hemingway, Louis, 1924, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 386)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 5/11
      See also: box 3, folder 159-163 box 16, folder 937
    - Hemingway, Samuel B., 1924, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Herter, Christian A.
      See: box 1, folder 1-11 box 1, folder 37 box 7, folder 408-409
    - Heuss, John, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - Hewes, James E., Jr., 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 389)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 8/3
    - Hiers, Richard, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Higginbotham, Lorine, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Higgins, Richard R., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Hill School
      See: box 2, folder 76
    - Hill, Clyde M., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Hill, Paul A., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - Hindemith, Paul, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - Hiscock, Ira V., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - Hobby, W. P.
    - Hohler, Gerald F., 1926 (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - Holborn, Hajo, 1941, 1956, 1958, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - Holden, Reuben, 1950, 1954-1955, 1957-1959, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 399)
    - Holliday, Samuel N., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 400)
    - Hollister, Burton J., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Holm, Fritz, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 402)
    - Holmes, Nathaniel, II, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 403)
      See also: box 15, folder 879-880
    - Holt, Hamilton, 1949-1950, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 404)
    - Holt, Henry, and Company, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 405)
    - Hooker, Davenport, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 406)
    - Hooker, Richard, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - Hooker, Thomas Jr., 1917 (Box 7, Folder 407a)
    - Hooper, Franklin H.
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1943 March-Apr, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 408)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1943 May, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 409)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 10/6
    - Hoover War Library
      See: box 9, folder 530-531
    - Horne, David
      See: box 9, folder 552-553
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 410)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 19/19
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 411)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 28/27
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 412)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 15/6
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1928 March-May (Box 7, Folder 413)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 23/16
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1928 June-July (Box 7, Folder 414)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 17/20
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1928 August-December (Box 7, Folder 415)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 22/17
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1929-1931 (Box 7, Folder 416)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 21/10
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1932-1939, 1941, 1942, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 417)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 18/18
    - House, Edward M.
      See: The Edward M. House Papers, MS 466 (Seymour-House Correspondence 1921-1937)
      See: Series II, Books, "The Intimate Papers of Colonel House," boxes 21-43
      See: Series II, Books, "Diary Letters from the Paris Peace Conference," boxes 44-46
      See: Series II, Articles, boxes 49-51
      See: Series II, Memoranda of Conversations, box 52
      See: Series II, Lectures, boxes 55-56
      See: Series III, Topical Files, boxes 60-65b
      See: Series IV, House Collection/Administration, boxes 83-86
    - House, Loulie (Mrs. Edward H.), 1919, 1928, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 418)
    - Houston, D. F., 1925 (Box 8, Folder 419)
    - Housum, Robert, undated (Box 8, Folder 420)
    - Howard, Chapin, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 421)
    - Howard, Harry N., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 422)
    - Howard, James M., 1952
    - Hubbard, Allen, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 424)
    - Hudson, Manley O., 1922, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 425)
    - Huebsch, B. W., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 426)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 427)
    - Hulburd, De Forest, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 428)
    - Hull, Cordell, 1937, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 429)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 2/4
    - Hunt, Richard C., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 430)
    - Hunting, Eleanor B. (Mrs. Ralph), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 431)
    - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 432)
    - Husted, Hal, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 433)
    - Hutchins, Robert M., 1923-1924 (Box 8, Folder 434)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 7/0
    - Ide, Charles E., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 435)
    - Imbrie, Katherine (Mrs. Robert W.), 1928 (Box 8, Folder 436)
    - Imperial War Museum, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 437)
    - Ims, Raymond, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 438)
    - The Independent, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 438a)
    - Indiana University, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 439)
    - Indiana University Press, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 440)
    - Institute for World Affairs
      See: box 8, folder 480
    - Institute of Politics, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 441)
    - Isaacs, Rufus D.
      See: box 11, folder 683
    - Isaacson, Pauline, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 442)
    - Izant, Grace G. (Mrs. Robert J.), 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 443)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 3/6
    - Jackson, Henry H., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 444)
    - Jackson, Percy, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 445)
    - Jacobus, Don, undated (Box 8, Folder 446)
    - Jameson, J. Franklin, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 446a)
    - James, Edward T.
      See: box 4, folder 237
    - James, William A.
    - Javits, Jacob K.
    - Jefferson, Howard B., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 447)
    - Jenks, John E., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 448)
    - Jennings, Newell, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 449)
    - Jenson, Cynthia, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 450)
    - Joerg, W. L. G., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 451)
    - Johns Hopkins Press, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 452)
    - Johnson, Allen, 1923-1924, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 453)
    - Johnson, Douglas, 1925, 1927-1928, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 454)
    - Johnson, George M., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 455)
    - Johnston, Waldo C. M., 1956, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 456)
    - Jones, F. S., 1913, 1917, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 457)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 0/5
    - Jones, Louise Seymour (Mrs. Rex), 1957
    - Jones, Payson, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 459)
    - Jones, Theodore S., 1952, undated (Box 8, Folder 460)
    - Jordan, Max, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 461)
    - Jusserand, J. A. A. J., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 462)
    - Kahnweiler, Bettina, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 463)
    - Kane, J. F., 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 464)
    - Keefe, Donald F.
      See: box 9, folder 541
    - Keen, W. W., 1917, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 465)
    - Kellogg, Vernon
      See: box 4, folder 179
    - Kemper, John M., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 466)
    - Kent, Sherman, 1942, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 467)
    - Keogh, Andrew, 1916, 1924, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 468)
    - Kerr, Chester, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 469)
    - Kerr, Philip
      See: box 9, folder 522
    - Keyes, Harold B., undated (Box 8, Folder 470)
    - Kilbourn, Orrin P., 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 471)
    - Kimball, Anna C.
      See: box 15, folder 892
    - Kimball, Joseph S., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 472)
    - Kimball, Winifred B.
      See: box 15, folder 886-888
    - Kimble, George H. T.
      See: box 2, folder 108
    - Kincaid, Carl, 1950, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 473)
    - King's College, Cambridge, 1926, 1954, 1956-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 474)
      Letters To CS/From CS: 17/1
    - Kinsey, Robert S., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 475)
    - Kiphuth, Robert, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 476)
    - Kisker, George W., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 477)
    - Klingberg, Frank J., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 478)
    - Klingel, M. P., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 479)
    - Klotsche, J. Martin, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 480)
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 481)
      See also: box 7, folder 408-409
    - Knox, H. S., 1927 (Box 8, Folder 482)
    - Kopelowicz, A., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 482a)
    - Kohler, Charlotte
      See: box 13, folder 841-842
    - Krafft, Herman F., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 483)
    - Kreisi, Hans M., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 484)
    - Krock, Arthur
      See: box 12, folder 772-774
    - Lamar, Howard R., 1957-1958, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 485)
    - Lamont, Thomas W., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 486)
    - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 486a)
    - Lane, Edwin S., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 487)
    - Langer, William L., 1929, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 488)